http://www.hockmeyer.com/privacy-policy

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation (Hockmeyer) values its users’ privacy. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) will help you understand how we collect and use personal information from those who visit our website and what we will and will not do with the information we collect. Our Policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet, but to exceed, most existing privacy standards.
We reserve the right to make changes to this Policy at any given time. If you want to make sure that you are up to date with the latest changes, we advise you to frequently visit this page. If at any point in time Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
This Policy applies to Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation, and it governs any and all data collection and usage by us. Through the use of www.hockmeyer.com , you are therefore consenting to the data collection procedures expressed in this Policy.
Please note that this Policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by us. If you visit a website that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent to better understand the way in which websites garner, make use of and share the information collected.
Specifically, this Policy will inform you of the following
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through our website;
Why we collect personally identifiable information and the legal basis for such collection;
How we use the collected information and with whom it may be shared;
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data; and
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
Information We Collect
It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. This website collects various types of information, such as information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and serverlogs.
In addition, Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation may have the occasion to collect non-personal anonymous demographic information, such as the type of browser you are using, IP address, or type of operating system, which will assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation may also deem it necessary, from time to time, to follow websites that our users may frequent to gleam what types of services and products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.
Why We Collect Information and For How Long
We are collecting your data for several reasons:
To better understand your needs and provide you with the services you have requested;
To fulfill our legitimate interest in improving our services and products;
To send you promotional emails containing information we think you may like when we have your consent to do so;
To contact you to fill out surveys or participate in other types of market research, when we have your consent to do so;
To customize our website according to your online behavior and personal preferences.
The data we collect from you will be stored for no longer than necessary. The length of time we retain said information will be determined based upon the following criteria: the length of time your personal information remains relevant; the length of time it is reasonable to keep records to demonstrate that we have fulfilled our duties and obligations; any limitation periods within which claims might be made; any retention periods prescribed by law or recommended by regulators, professional bodies or associations; the type of contract we have with you, the existence of your consent, and our legitimate interest in keeping such information as stated in this Policy.
Use of Information Collected
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of its customer lists and/or names to any third parties.
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.hockmeyer.com
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation uses various third-party social media features including but not limited to LinkedIn, YouTube and other interactive programs. These may collect your IP address and require cookies to work properly. These services are governed by the privacy policies of the providers and are not within HockmeyerEquipment Corporation’s control.
Disclosure of Information
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation may not use or disclose the information provided by you except under the following circumstances:
in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined;
as required by law, or in response to a subpoena or search warrant;
to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;
as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service;
as necessary to maintain, safeguard and preserve all the rights and property of Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation.
Non-Marketing Purposes
HockmeyerEquipmentCorporationgreatlyrespectsyourprivacy.Wedomaintainandreserve the right to contact you if needed for non-marketing purposes (such as bug alerts, security breaches, account issues, and/or changes in Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation products and services). In certain circumstances, we may use our website, newspapers, or other public means to post a notice.
Children under the age of 13
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation’s website is not directed to, and does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from, children under the age of thirteen (13). If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database, or in the alternative, that verifiable parental consent is obtained for the use and storage of such information. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communications from us by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe from our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to unsubscribe@hockmeyer.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third-party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe or opt-out. Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation will continue to adhere to this Policy with respect to any personal information previously collected.
Links to Other Websites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites.Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.
Security
Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (e.g. credit card information), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the webpage.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. This is all done to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.
Acceptance of Terms
By using this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you agree and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: sales@hockmeyer.com
Mailing Address: Hockmeyer Equipment Corporation 610 Supor Blvd Harrison, New Jersey 07029
Privacy Links
Cookie Settings
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
This website uses cookies to enhance your experience (such as viewing videos).
If you click the "Allow All" button you agree to having those cookies set on your device.
If you do not wish to accept cookies from this website, you can choose to not by updating your browser preferences or clicking "Disable All".
For more information on how we use Cookies, please read our Privacy Policy.
Cookie Settings
Disable All
Allow All
We noticed that your preferred language is not English. In order to translate this page, please use a browser that supports auto translations such as: Google Chrome or Microsoft Edge.
